[{"answer": "You jerking off or just pissed", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Get your gear on", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Torch it over there", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Screw the dogs!! Torch it!", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Magnesium of some type... or some kind of strange alloy.  And those poor dumb bastards had to go and blow the hell out of it", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You know damn well what we both make of it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "...I think the whole process would have taken an hour... maybe more. And then I suppose both would have changed back to dog form", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Of course not... But whatever it was revived, it... Well, The Thing was probably disoriented... and realized it couldn't survive for long in our atmosphere... But being the incredibly adaptable creature it was... it tried to become something that could... Before the Norwegians killed it... it somehow got to this dog", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What was he doing in the rec room", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, where was he? Where did he go", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend, how long would it take you to strap those big fou", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Then get a move on. Childs, come with me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What you doin'", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Well, who the hell you think wants to get in there with you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That's impossible, man! Okay, my friend, out of the john where I can see you", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " my friend, you come on out here!", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Let's just not get worried about anything just now", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " After all this mess", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No. Just let him freeze out there", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Then we're wrong", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " You ain't tying me up", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Then kill me", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Get back!", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Screw the generator!", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Maybe it ain't coming", "docId": "Thing_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Bet the last place you ever go", "qsentId": 26}]